Frank and Walt Cartoons
Frank and Walt Cartoons
1966
Frank and Walt
2 linear ft.
46 original cartoons from the kids' puzzle and activity strip Tom Trick.
2661241
Biographical History
The Tom Trick kids' puzzle and activity strip was written by Meg and drawn by Frank and Walt. The strip was distributed by the NEA syndicate in the mid 1960s.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Frank and Walt Cartoons collection contains 46 original Sunday cartoons from the kids' puzzle and activity strip Tom Trick (1966).
Arrangement of the Collection
Cartoons are in chronological order.
Related Material
has collections of over one hundred cartoonists. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Frank and Walt.; Newspaper Enterprise Association.; Tom Trick (comic strip); Art -- Cartoonists; American wit and humor, Pictorial.; Caricatures and cartoons -- United States.; Cartoonists -- United States.; Comic books, strips, etc. -- United States.; Cartoons (humorous images); Cartoonists.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Inventory
- Tom Trick cartoons, 46 items; "Written by Meg, Drawn by Frank & Walt"; (traces of blue pencil, pen and ink, red ink, opaque white, paste-overs on illustration board, approx. 14 ½ x 23 in.)
  - 01/30/1966 (Box 1)
  - 02/06/1966 (Box 1)
  - 02/20/1966 (Box 1)
  - 02/27/1966 (Box 1)
  - 03/06/1966 (Box 1)
  - 03/13/1966 (Box 1)
  - 03/20/1966 (Box 1)
  - 03/27/1966 (Box 1)
  - 04/03/1966 (Box 1)
  - 04/10/1966 (Box 1)
  - 04/17/1966 (Box 1)
  - 04/24/1966 (Box 1)
  - 05/01/1966 (Box 1)
  - 05/08/1966 (Box 1)
  - 05/15/1966 (Box 1)
  - 05/22/1966 (Box 1)
  - 06/05/1966 (Box 1)
  - 06/12/1966 (Box 1)
  - 06/19/1966 (Box 1)
  - 06/26/1966 (Box 1)
  - 07/03/1966 (Box 1)
  - 07/10/1966 (Box 1)
  - 07/17/1966 (Box 1)
  - 07/24/1966 (Box 1)
  - 07/31/1966 (Box 1)
  - 08/07/1966 (Box 1)
  - 08/14/1966 (Box 1)
  - 08/21/1966 (Box 1)
  - 08/28/1966 (Box 1)
  - 09/04/1966 (Box 1)
  - 09/11/1966 (Box 1)
  - 09/18/1966 (Box 1)
  - 09/25/1966 (Box 1)
  - 10/02/1966 (Box 1)
  - 10/09/1966 (Box 1)
  - 10/16/1966 (Box 1)
  - 10/23/1966 (Box 1)
  - 10/30/1966 (Box 1)
  - 11/06/1966 (Box 1)
  - 11/13/1966, ("Written by Meg, Drawn by Frank") (Box 1)
  - 11/20/1966, ("Written by Meg, Drawn by Frank") (Box 1)
  - 11/27/1966, ("Written by Meg, Drawn by Frank") (Box 1)
  - 12/04/1966, ("Written by Meg, Drawn by Frank") (Box 1)
  - 12/11/1966, ("Written by Meg, Drawn by Frank") (Box 1)
  - 12/18/1966, ("Written by Meg, Drawn by Frank") (Box 1)
  - 12/25/1966, ("Written by Meg, Drawn by Frank") (Box 1)